Guide to the Douglas Killgore video materials, 1911-2013 UA 405
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Media
  - BIOE 301, Tape 4, (DV), 2007-06-28 (Box 5)
  - William Lawson / The Relationship Between Religion and Government, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-07-11 (Box 5)
  - Dave Katten Project, Health Services #4, (DV), 2007-07-16 (Box 5)
  - KPFT Boniuk Center #1, (DV), 2007-07-20 (Box 5)
  - KPFT Boniuk Center #2, (DV), 2007-07-20 (Box 5)
  - Zubarev, (DV), 2007-07-24 (Box 5)
  - Health Services Presentation; Student Interview Clips, Rice, (DVD), 2007-08-20 (Box 5)
  - Hersch; Schlosser; Owlspace; Video Conference, (DVD), 2007-08-28 (Box 5)
  - McMurtry College Groundbreaking (2), (DVD), 2007-08-28 (Box 5)
  - McMurtry College Groundbreaking, Tape 1, (DV ), 2007-08-29 (Box 5)
  - Gonzales Sci Prof, (DV), 2007-09-02 (Box 5)
  - Bones of Contention: Exhibiting "Lucy" at the HMNS, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-09-06 (Box 5)
  - Vivek Sarkar / Programming Challenges for Petascale and Multicore Parallel Systems, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-09-12 (Box 5)
  - Paulraj Arogyaswami / India Awakes: Opportunities for US High Technology Enterprise, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-09-13 (Box 5)
  - Live Interactive Demos Featuring Research of ECE Students, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-09-13 (Box 5)
  - Students' Demo Elec., (DV), 2007-09-13 (Box 5)
  - Athanasiou Sci Engr Update, (DV), 2007-09-24 (Box 5)
  - Douglas Natelson faculty interview, (DV), 2007-09-24 (Box 5)
  - Paul Hamilton, Daslav Brkic / Engineering and Construction Global Forum, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-09-25 (Box 5)
  - Duncan College Groundbreaking (4), Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Student Interviews, Health Services Program, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Harvey Project, (DV), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Chris Munoz interview, (DV), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Keck Lecture, (DV), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Duncan College Ground-Breaking, (DV), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Colvin, Dearberger, (DV), 2007-09-27 (Box 5)
  - Joan Strassman / Prairie Chickens, Etc., Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-10 (Box 5)
  - More Interviewees for Harvey [Scholars] Video, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-10 (Box 5)
  - Data Backup: Science and Engr. Update, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-10 (Box 5)
  - Shepherd School flutists, (DV), 2007-10-04 (Box 5)
  - Science and Engineering Alumni Reception, Santa Fe (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Tree relocation, Autry Court, (DV), 2007-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Joan Strassman, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-10-08 (Box 5)
  - Jessica M. Logan / Brain and Behavior: How we Create and Maintain Memory, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-10-09 (Box 5)
  - Seeing Through Clutter, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-10-10 (Box 5)
  - Abdul Kalam, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-10-18 (Box 5)
  - Ruth J. Simmons / Relating to Civil Rights, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-10-19 (Box 5)
  - Alix Ohlin / The Tempest of Nature and Art, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-10-23 (Box 5)
  - Alix Ohlin, (DV), 2007-10-24 (Box 5)
  - Alix Ohlin, (DV), 2007-10-25 (Box 5)
  - Eileen Collins, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-10-27 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk Media Center, (DV), 2007-10-27 (Box 5)
  - Froggy Wins #1, (DV ), 2007-10-28 (Box 5)
  - Dan T. Gillespie / Stochastic Chemical Kinetics, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-11-05 (Box 5)
  - Harvey, B. Hasset, (DV), 2007-11-08 (Box 5)
  - Master of Liberal Studies Capstone Presentation, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-11-13 (Box 5)
  - Capstone lecture, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-11-13 (Box 5)
  - Capstone lecture, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-11-13 (Box 5)
  - UH Melcher Hall, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-11-14 (Box 5)
  - Amazing Faiths Dinner, (DV), 2007-11-15 (Box 5)
  - Richard Smith / Beyond Borders: Engaging Transnational China, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-11-26 (Box 5)
  - William Calvin / How to Treat Global Fever, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-11-29 (Box 5)
  - Paula Sanders / Community, Culture and Tolerance in a Medieval Islamic Society, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-12-02 (Box 5)
  - Rice Lego Robot Contest, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-12-02 (Box 5)
  - Rice Lego Robot Contest, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-12-02 (Box 5)
  - Vivek Sarkar / Parallel Sortware for Mainstream Computing, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-12-05 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2007-12-06 (Box 5)
  - Computer Science, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-12-11 (Box 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Video Demo (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-12-17 (Box 5)
  - Who Knew (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-12-20 (Box 5)
  - Harvey Scholars, 2007-2008, Rice IT/Friends of Fondren, (DVD) (Box 5)
  - NanoGuin, Killgore, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Honors, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - Rice Football Yesterday and Today, Rice IT, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - Senior Engineering Projects, 2008: Arctic Ambulance; Engineers Without Borders, (DVD) (Box 5)
  - Tunafest 2008: Sus-Tuna-Bility (4), Rice IT, (DVD) (Box 5)
  - Laureates slide show, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - MOB Demo version 5.04, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - campus scenes- azaleas - Virgil video?, (DV), 2008 (Box 6)
  - Robert Curl interviewed by Cyrus Mody, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk Center Promo Rough Assembly #1, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-01-22 (Box 5)
  - Movie Photos; Fitlow 2 Students and campus, (DVD), 2008-01-23 (Box 5)
  - John Boles #1, (DV), 2008-01-23 (Box 6)
  - Boles #2, (DV), 2008-01-23 (Box 6)
  - Paul Padley Aud Response, (DV), 2008-01-25 (Box 6)
  - Rachel Kimbro ARS, (DV), 2008-01-29 (Box 5)
  - Angela Rabuck OwlSpace, (DV), 2008-01-31 (Box 6)
  - Selcuk Akturk DH 1064, (DV), 2008-02-12 (Box 6)
  - Selcuk Akturk, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-02-13 (Box 6)
  - 30-second spot, 2006, master dub, (DV), 2008-02-22 (Box 5)
  - John Boles / Lovett to Leebron, master dub, (DV), 2008-02-22 (Box 5)
  - Robert Curl interviewed by Cyrus Mody (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-02-26 (Box 4)
  - AFP dinner dialogues, Houston Chronicle footage, (DVD), 2008-02-26 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk #1, RAC, (DV), 2008-02-26 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #2, RAC, (DV), 2008-02-26 (Box 6)
  - Curl #1, (DV), 2008-02-26 (Box 5)
  - ARS class #2, (DV), 2008-02-27 (Box 5)
  - ECE Pres. Prof Lec, (DV), 2008-02-27 (Box 5)
  - Hackerman Symposium - lunch, (DV), 2008-02-28 (Box 5)
  - Hackerman Symposium, Pt 2, (DV), 2008-02-28 (Box 6)
  - Hackerman Symposium, Pt 2 Panel A, (DV), 2008-02-28 (Box 6)
  - Hackerman Symposium, Pt 2 Panel B, (DV), 2008-02-28 (Box 6)
  - Hackerman Symposium -lunch, (DV), 2008-02-28 (Box 6)
  - Qianfan Xu, faculty talk, (DV), 2008-02-29 (Box 6)
  - Curl #2, (DV), 2008-03 (Box 5)
  - Vanessa Sih, faculty talk, (DV), 2008-03-05 (Box 5)
  - Peter Catrysse, faculty talk, (DV), 2008-03-07 (Box 6)
  - Tech in Classroom, Dance Theatre students, (DV), 2008-03-13 (Box 5)
  - Monica Biernet, tape 2, (DV), 2008-03-14 (Box 6)
  - Monica Biernat lecture, (DV), 2008-03-14 (Box 6)
  - Terry Graham, Ed Tech Podium, (DV), 2008-03-17 (Box 6)
  - Phil Montgomery and Claire B[artlett], (DV), 2008-03-17 (Box 6)
  - Jason Hafner / Teaching with Tech, (DV), 2008-03-17 (Box 6)
  - Martel lecture in Gender and Science, Tape 1 of 2, (DV), 2008-03-18 (Box 6)
  - Martel lecture in Gender and Science, Tape 2 of 2, (DV), 2008-03-18 (Box 6)
  - David Lange, (DV), 2008-03-18 (Box 5)
  - Brian Grandy, (DV), 2008-03-19 (Box 6)
  - Robert Curl interviewed by Cyrus Mody (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-03-20 (Box 5)
  - Curl #3, (DV), 2008-03-20 (Box 5)
  - Curl #3, pt2, (DV), 2008-03-20 (Box 5)
  - Curl #1, (DV), 2008-03-20 (Box 5)
  - Hello, Hamlet! Wiess #1, (DV), 2008-03-21 (Box 6)
  - Hello, Hamlet! Wiess #2, (DV), 2008-03-21 (Box 6)
  - CRC Topping Out, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-03-24 (Box 5)
  - Topping Out Ceremony, CRC, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Lab in a Backpack #2, (DV), 2008-03-24 (Box 6)
  - High school students visit Rice, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-03-27 (Box 5)
  - High school students visit Rice, Tape 2, (DV), 2008-04-01 (Box 5)
  - High school students visit Rice, Tape 3, (DV), 2008-04-01 (Box 5)
  - Curl #1, (DV), 2008-04-03 (Box 5)
  - Curl #2, (DV), 2008-04-03 (Box 5)
  - Tom Jones for P. Reiff, tape 1 of 2, (DV), 2008-04-07 (Box 6)
  - Tom Jones for P. Reiff, tape 1 of 2, (DV), 2008-04-07 (Box 6)
  - EdTech Video Conference, (DV), 2008-04-09 (Box 6)
  - Willy Statue video party, (DV), 2008-04-11 (Box 6)
  - Rebecca Valz and Phil Montgomery, (DV), 2008-04-11 (Box 6)
  - Claire Bartlett lunch and PDF footage, (DV), 2008-04-18 (Box 6)
  - Phil Bedient's class, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-04-22 (Box 6)
  - Phil Bedient's class, Tape 2, (DV), 2008-04-22 (Box 6)
  - Brochstein Pavilion Dedication (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-04-24 (Box 5)
  - Innovate poster session, (DV), 2008-04-25 (Box 6)
  - Brochstein Pavilion Opening, (DV), 2008-04-28 (Box 6)
  - Teaching with Tech #1, (DV), 2008-04-30 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk Art Show, (DV), 2008-04-30 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk S+S, (DV), 2008-05-01 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk St. Stephens #2, (DV), 2008-05-01 (Box 6)
  - Teach with Tech, MECH 407, (DV), 2008-05-05 (Box 6)
  - V. Arbitzu, Teach with Tech, (DV), 2008-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Solis, Ed Tech interview, (DV), 2008-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Laureates Dinner (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-05-10 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2008-05-15 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk, Rabbi #1, (DV), 2008-05-15 (Box 6)
  - Carlos [Solis?] ,OwlSpace, (DV), 2008-05-22 (Box 6)
  - Robert Curl interviewed by Cyrus Mody (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-05-29 (Box 5)
  - Instructional Videos from EdTech final cut, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-05-29 (Box 5)
  - Curl #1, (DV), 2008-05-29 (Box 5)
  - Curl #2, (DV), 2008-05-29 (Box 5)
  - Curl, Baker Inst. #2, (DV), 2008-05-30 (Box 5)
  - Humboldt Symposium: The Universe and World Around Us, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-05-31 (Box 5)
  - Curl #7, Humb. Symposium, (DV), 2008-05-31 (Box 5)
  - Terry Graham at work, (DV), 2008-06-05 (Box 6)
  - Physics Bldg, (DV), 2008-06-06 (Box 6)
  - Physics Bldg. kick-off, (DV), 2008-06-06 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #5 of 15, (DV), 2008-06-20 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #1 of 15, (DV), 2008-06-23 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #2 of 15, (DV), 2008-06-24 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #3 of 15, (DV), 2008-06-25 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #4 of 15, (DV), 2008-06-26 (Box 6)
  - South Plant Stack Tower Installation (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-06-28 (Box 5)
  - Tower Erection, tape 1, (DV), 2008-06-28 (Box 6)
  - Tower Erection, tape 2, (DV), 2008-06-28 (Box 6)
  - Tower Erection, Tape 3, (DV), 2008-06-28 (Box 6)
  - Tower Erection, Big Mov, raw footage, (DVD), 2008-06-28 (Box 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Video (3) Edited Master and photos, xlfilms, (DVD), 2008-07-01 (Box 5)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #6 of 15, (DV), 2008-07-10 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #7 of 15, (DV), 2008-07-10 (Box 6)
  - SCS AP Program, Siva Kumari, #8 of 15, (DV), 2008-07-11 (Box 6)
  - Robert Curl interviewed by Cyrus Mody, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-08-06 (Box 5)
  - Curl #1, (DV), 2008-08-06 (Box 5)
  - Curl #2, (DV), 2008-08-06 (Box 5)
  - Tunafest 2008, partial source, (DVD), 2008-08-07 (Box 5)
  - Peggy Whitson, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-08-28 (Box 5)
  - SCS. Mary McIntyre, (DV), 2008-09-02 (Box 5)
  - Nano #4, (DV), 2008-09-03 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Susie Glasscock, (DV), 2008-09-03 (Box 5)
  - Lancer Presentations - Curl, Tour, Ajayan, Colvin, Pasquali, and Murdock, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-09-04 (Box 5)
  - Lancer #1, Nano, Kyle Morrow Room, (DV), 2008-09-04 (Box 5)
  - Lancer, Smalley Inst., Kyle Morrow #3, (DV), 2008-09-04 (Box 5)
  - SCS, David Leebron, (DV), 2008-09-07 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian / Faculty Search Committee Discussion, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian / Interactional Fairness; Power Effectiveness and Gender raw footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 2, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 3, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 4, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 5, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Valian, Tape 6, (DV), 2008-09-10 (Box 5)
  - CONTACT lectures for Nano, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-09-11 (Box 6)
  - CONTACT lectures for Nano, Tape 2, (DV), 2008-09-11 (Box 6)
  - CONTACT lectures for Nano, Tape 3, (DV), 2008-09-11 (Box 6)
  - CONTACT lectures for Nano, Tape 4, (DV), 2008-09-11 (Box 6)
  - Boles interview, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-09-18 (Box 6)
  - Jiming Bao, faculty talk, (DV), 2008-09-22 (Box 5)
  - David del Pino, Rayzor #1, (DV), 2008-09-24 (Box 6)
  - SCS, Olson class, (DV), 2008-10-01 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins #2, (DV), 2008-10-01 (Box 6)
  - Kathleen Matthews clip, (DV), 2008-10-02 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins #1, (DV), 2008-10-02 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins #2, (DV), 2008-10-02 (Box 6)
  - Student picnic, (DV), 2008-10-07 (Box 6)
  - Callie Project, (DV), 2008-10-08 (Box 6)
  - Lino Tagliapietra, (DV), 2008-10-13 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 1, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 2, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 3, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 4, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 5, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 6, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Houston Air Conference, Tape 7 - Lunch Talk, (DV), 2008-10-16 (Box 6)
  - Sally Ride event, (DV), 2008-10-18 (Box 6)
  - Glasscock School 40th anniversary, final cut (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-10-21 (Box 5)
  - Glasscock AP Academies (2), (DVD), 2008-10-21 (Box 5)
  - Utility Cart Video Dub, (DV), 2008-10-22 (Box 6)
  - Shanker lecture, (DV), 2008-10-30 (Box 6)
  - Tudor Fieldhouse Dedication, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-11-07 (Box 5)
  - Tudor Fieldhouse Dedication, Tape 1 of 2, (DV), 2008-11-07 (Box 6)
  - Tudor Fieldhouse Dedication, Tape 2 of 2, (DV), 2008-11-07 (Box 5)
  - Teach with Tech, Lunch #1, (DV), 2008-11-09 (Box 6)
  - Nicole Ramsey / China Olympics raw footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-11-10 (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Sharpe lecture, Tape 2 of 2, (DV), 2008-11-10 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Soc Heard (2), (DV), 2008-11-11 (Box 6)
  - Reception Honoring Dean Kathleen Matthews, Rice Media, (DVD), 2008-11-12 (Box 5)
  - Kathleen Matthews retirement, (DV), 2008-11-13 (Box 6)
  - Ratna Sarkar / Socrates, (DV), 2008-11-20 (Box 6)
  - Olson / Revised Unconventional Wisdom, Rice, (DVD), 2008-12 (Box 5)
  - O'Bryan 121709.mov, Ed Tech lecture, (DVD), 2008-12-17 (Box 5)
  - Teach with Tech, Wii #1, (DV), 2008-12-17 (Box 6)
  - Teach with Tech, Wii #2, (DV), 2008-12-17 (Box 6)
  - Teach with Tech video feed, (DV), 2008-12-17 (Box 6)
  - Curl, (DV), 2008-12-18 (Box 5)
  - REEP Siva, Kenya Project #1, (DV), 2008-12-19 (Box 6)
  - James Cuno / The Promise of Museums, Part 2, (DVD), 2009 (Box 6)
  - Ray Anderson / Sustainability in Action, DeLange Conference 2009 (2), (DVD) (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1 (2), (DVD) (Box 6)
  - Commencement, Doctoral,, (DV), 2009 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, 2f, Part 9, (DVD) (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Parts 1a-e, (DVD) (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1, (DVD) (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Parts 1-2, (DVD) (Box 6)
  - Mina Intro, Lab in a Backpack, (DV), 2009 (Box 6)
  - Carlos Soc Ed Tech in camera, (DV), 2009 (Box 6)
  - Delange 2009 #1, (DV) (Box 6)
  - Delange 2009 #2, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #3, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #4, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #5, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #6 (2), (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #7, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #8, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #9, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #10, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #11, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #12, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #13, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #14, (DV) (Box 6)
  - DeLange 2009 #15, (DV) (Box 6)
  - M2P to backup, (DVD), 2009 (Box 6)
  - Gaza Crisis, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-01-15 (Box 6)
  - Gaza Crisis #1, (DV), 2009-01-16 (Box 6)
  - Gaza Crisis #2, (DV), 2009-01-16 (Box 6)
  - Campus ministers assn., (DV), 2009-01-31 (Box 6)
  - Conversation with Dr. Bill, (DVD), 2009-01-31 (Box 6)
  - Ask the Experts #1, (DV), 2009-02-04 (Box 6)
  - Robert M. O'Neil / Speech in the University (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-02-05 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk IT Ask Expert?, (DV), 2009-02-05 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2009-02-05 (Box 6)
  - IT Ask Expert .m2p, (DVD), 2009-02-09 (Box 6)
  - Teach with Tech #1, (DV), 2009-02-18 (Box 6)
  - Wiess West Side [Story] #1, (DV), 2009-02-18 (Box 6)
  - Rebecca Richards-Kortum / Engineering Sustainable Innovations to Prevent Cancer, Rice Media Ed Tech, (DVD), 2009-02-19 (Box 6)
  - REEP#2, Kenya, (DV), 2009-02-24 (Box 6)
  - Leebron Town Hall #1, (DV), 2009-02-24 (Box 6)
  - Leebron Town Hall #2, (DV), 2009-02-24 (Box 6)
  - Kenya Project, Information Session, (DV), 2009-02-24 (Box 6)
  - West Side Story, (DV), 2009-02-25 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1b, Disc 2 Rees and Bruegmann, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-02 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1c, Disc 3 McCarty, Jaffee, Leebron, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-02 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1b, Disc 4; Leebron, Sassen NOT USED, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-02 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1d, Disc 4/Leebron, Sassen, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-02 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 1d, Disc 4 / Anderson, Kotkin (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-02 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Parts 1 and 2, (DVD), 2009-03-03 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 3a, Disc 10, (DVD), 2009-03-04 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 3b, Disc 11, (DVD), 2009-03-04 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 4 (2), (DVD), 2009-03-04 (Box 6)
  - Nikolas Rose / Neuropolitics in the 21st Century, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-09 (Box 6)
  - REEP #1, (DV), 2009-03-14 (Box 6)
  - Alexander Tsesis / Inciting Hatred, Dehumanization and Genocide, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - RHS Boles #1, (DV), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - RHS Boles #2, (DV), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Lab in a Backpack #1, (DV), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2009-03-24 (Box 6)
  - Rice Dance Studio #1, (DV), 2009-03-25 (Box 6)
  - HISD News Today: Davila Elem. School Conference at Rice, (DVD), 2009-03-25 (Box 6)
  - Dance #3, (DV), 2009-03-25 (Box 6)
  - Rice Dance Studio, (DV), 2009-03-25 (Box 6)
  - Rice Dance Students #2, (DV), 2009-03-25 (Box 6)
  - Mina Intro, Lab in a Backpack #1, (DV), 2009-03-28 (Box 6)
  - POI Grand Meeting interviews; Kortum #2, (DV), 2009-04-01 (Box 5)
  - Tracy Voltz [Volz] on PPT pres., (DV), 2009-04-03 (Box 6)
  - Tracy Volz slides only PPT, (DV), 2009-04-03 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Parts 1a, 1b, 1c, 1d, 1e (2), (DVD), 2009-04-15 (Box 6)
  - Viqui #1, (DV), 2009-04-15 (Box 6)
  - Ken Kennedy lecture, (DVD), 2009-04-19 (Box 6)
  - Jenny Reardon/Reep Kopp, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-04-21 (Box 6)
  - Jenny Reardon / Finding Oprah's Roots, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-04-21 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Part 8, (DVD), 2009-04-28 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Parts 2c-d, Disc 7 (2), (DVD), 2009-04-29 (Box 6)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup, Boniuk 2, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-07 (Box 7)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup, SCS 40th Anniversary, Video, stills. Mov files, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-07 (Box 7)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup, Rice Stock Footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-07 (Box 7)
  - Data Backup: Procoder Out backup, SCS 40th Anniv., stills, Rice Media, (DVD ), 2009-05-07 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder out, stock footage, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-07 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder out, Boniuk2, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-07 (Box 6)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup Harvey Scholars Stills, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 7)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup IT AskExperts20409, Jones School, Lab In A Backpack, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 7)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup, Rice Stock MovA, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 7)
  - PROCODER OUT Backup Connexions, Construction, DeLange Dkstorage, EDTech, Engineering, Finder Notes, Football pix, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 7)
  - Data Backup: Procoder Out, Connexions, Construction Images, DeLange, Dkstorage, EdTech, Engineering, Finder Notes, Football Pix, Rice Media Services, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder out, Rice StockMovA, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder out, Harvey scholars stills, Rice Media, (DVD ), 2009-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder out, Ask Experts, Jones School, Lab in a Backpack, Office Work, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-08 (Box 6)
  - Doug's Backups: .m2ps, 2008 Bowl Program, Harvey video, RHS Kirby, Shell CS Lunch, Shell CSPart 1, Utility Carts, (DVD), 2009-05-13 (Box 6)
  - Doug's Backups: Kennedy at Rice, Lancer Ajayan, Lancer Colvin, McMurtry Groundbreaking, NanoGuin, (DVD), 2009-05-13 (Box 7)
  - Doug's Backups: .m2p, 80 Years Rice Athletics, Boniuk Rough 1 and 2, Language of God, 12109 Rendr, (DVD), 2009-05-13 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: LabInABackpack, OfficeWork, Tom's Backups, Databases, Disparities in Health, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-14 (Box 7)
  - C. Sidney Burrus / From FFTs to Wavelets, Rice Media Ed Tech, (DVD), 2009-05-20 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Procoder Out, Dr. Bill, Dean Matthews, Gottshcalk music, students in labs, Shepherd School, Tom in Osaka, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-21 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Harvey Video and Stills, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-21 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Ping/Leebron Video Slips 2006, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-21 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: LabInABackpack, EdTechVids, CRCTopoff, Dance, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-22 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Alumni2, Curl Interview, Sally Ride, Shell CSHouAir, Stills Doug Transfer, Backpack Titles in Spanish, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-27 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: NanoDS (Deb Smalley), Dogfight, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-27 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Ethnic Houston Music, LegLab2005, RiceSpot, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Conversation with Dr. Bill.mov, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: AP Academies, EdTech Lunch MisraB.mov, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Harvey Video, OwlSpace, PodiumA, Rice Engr Outreach3, PodiumH, Picnic2, ESL Classes, Marrs/AskExpert, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - DeLange Conference 2009, Day 2 Backup (2), (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: EWOBord13, Scrubster, Dance, Spanish LabInABackpack, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-05-28 (Box 6)
  - Lab in a Backpack (2), (DVD) 2009-05-29/2009-10-01 (Box 6)
  - Data Backup: Lehman2A, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-06-01 (Box 5)
  - Lab in a Backpack Instruction Video English and Spanish (2), (DVD), 2009-06-06 (Box 6)
  - Tom Killian, (DV), 2009-07-15 (Box 6)
  - Tom Killian's Physics Lab, Working with Lasers, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-07-16 (Box 6)
  - David Leebron, BRC, (DV), 2009-07-27 (Box 6)
  - BRC Signing and Tour; Texas Children's Hospital, (DVD), 2009-07-27 (Box 6)
  - CORRUL web video #1, (DV), 2009-07-28 (Box 6)
  - CORRUL web video #2, (DV), 2009-07-28 (Box 6)
  - CORRUL Project #3, (DV), 2009-07-28 (Box 6)
  - #2, Kyle Morrow Room, (DV), 2009-08-04 (Box 6)
  - Angie OwlSpace, (DV), 2009-08-20 (Box 6)
  - Elaine Ecklund interview CORRUL, (DV), 2009-08-24 (Box 6)
  - Michael Lindsay and Michael Emerson interviews, Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-08-28 (Box 6)
  - John McDevitt presentation @ BRC Speaker, (DV), 2009-08-28 (Box 6)
  - John McDevitt presentation @ BRC PPT, (DV), 2009-08-28 (Box 6)
  - John McDevitt presentation @ BRC c1pt2, (DV), 2009-08-28 (Box 6)
  - CORRUL Videos, .mov files; Bratter, Echlund, Lindsay, Emerson (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-08-31 (Box 6)
  - Meyer Minchen / The Berlin Airlift (4), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-09-01 (Box 6)
  - Weissenberger #1, (DV), 2009-09-01 (Box 6)
  - Carlos class, (DV), 2009-09-03 (Box 6)
  - Duncan College Sneak Peek (2), Rice Media (1), (DVD), 2009-09-08 (Box 6)
  - McMurtry College Sneak Peek (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2009-09-08 (Box 6)
  - McMurtry and Duncan Colleges sneak peek, (DV), 2009-09-08 (Box 6)
  - Gary Kidney / Let's Talk about Learning, (DVD), 2009-09-10 (Box 6)